Bob Bullock Comptroller of Public Accounts papers, Inclusive: 1970-1991, Bulk: 1975-1990
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Correspondence, 1975-1990; 1
  - Executive, 1989-1990; 2
    - Rule, Scott, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 18)
    - Rundell, J.L. “Skippy”, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 19)
    - Rushing, Brandon, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 20)
    - Russell, Barbara, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 21)
    - Russell, Sam W., 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 22)
    - Ryan, Terry, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 23)
    - Ryland, Cynthia Faulk, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 24)
    - Sacks, Sanford, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 25)
    - Salazar, Mr. & Mrs. Benito, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 26)
    - Saldivar, Sam, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 27)
    - Sams, Scott, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 28)
    - Sanchez, Robert P., 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 29)
    - Sanders, Mike, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 30)
    - Sanders-Castro, Judith A., 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 31)
    - Sansom, Andrew, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 32)
    - Santiago, JoAnna E., 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 33)
    - Santiesteban, H. Tati, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 34)
    - Santos, Arnulfo “Fito”, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 35)
    - Santos, Rogelio Hernandez, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 36)
    - Santos, Sandra R., 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 37)
    - Sasser, A. Ford III, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 38)
    - Sasser, Ross, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 39)
    - Satterwhite, W.T., 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 40)
    - Savage, Rich, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 41)
    - Sawyer, Mr. & Mrs. G. Ray, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 42)
    - Scharrer, Gary, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 43)
    - Schattel, Donald L., 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 44)
    - Schepps, Harmon, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 45)
    - Scheske, Robert B. “Bob”, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 46)
    - Schieffer, J. Thomas, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Schilt, Alexander F., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Schlueter, Stan, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Schmidt, Randall, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Schnabel, Charles, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Schoolcraft, Alan L., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Schulz, C.A., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Schulz, Charles, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Schwartz, Aaron R., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Schwartz, Walter C., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Scott, Ava, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - Scott, Morin M., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 12)
    - Scott, Wallace H. Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 13)
    - Scott, Willie L. ( Maj. Gen.), 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 14)
    - Scragg, George H. Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 15)
    - Seals, Woodrow B., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 16)
    - Seeger, Ruth, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 17)
    - Segal, Adrienne, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 18)
    - Seidlits, Curtis, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 19)
    - Sepulveda, Frank Sr., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 20)
    - Shamburger, W.M., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 21)
    - Sharp, John, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 22)
    - Sharp, John S., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 23)
    - Sharpe, Edwin R., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 24)
    - Sharpe, Fran, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 25)
    - Shaw, Nancy, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 26)
    - Shaw, Noble B., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 27)
    - Sheeran, Kevin, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 28)
    - Shepherd, Kathy, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 29)
    - Shepperd, John Ben, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 30)
    - Shipley, Donald K., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 31)
    - Shipley, Wayne, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 32)
    - Shivers, Allan “Bud”, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 33)
    - Shivers, Allan Sr., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 34)
    - Short, Alex H. Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 35)
    - Shropshire, Doris, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 36)
    - Silva, Antonio V., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 37)
    - Simmons, Wayland A., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 38)
    - Simpson, Harold B., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 39)
    - Sims, Everett Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 40)
    - Sims, Sherry, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 41)
    - Sims, William M., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 42)
    - Sirota, David, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 43)
    - Slider, James L., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 44)
    - Smith, Albert Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 45)
    - Smith, Bert Kruger, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 46)
    - Smith, Bettye R., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 47)
    - Smith, Bob, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 48)
    - Smith, Rev. & Mrs. C.B.T., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 49)
    - Smith, David, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 50)
    - Smith, E. Jack Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 51)
    - Smith, Frederick W., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 52)
    - Smith, George J., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 53)
    - Smith, J. David, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 54)
    - Smith, John S., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 55)
    - Smith, Lamar, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 56)
    - Smith, L.G. “Skip”, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 57)
    - Smith, Linda Moore, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 58)
    - Smith, Charles Claybourne, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 59)
    - Smith, R. Clint, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 60)
    - Smith, Raphael, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 61)
    - Smith, Richard C., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 62)
    - Smith, Sharon R., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 63)
    - Smith, Shearn, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 64)
    - Smith, Thomas E., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 65)
    - Smith, W. Forrest, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 66)
    - Smith, Mr. & Mrs. Weldon, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 67)
    - Smith, William R., 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 68)
    - Snodgrass, William R., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Snokhous, Raymond J., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Snyder, James L., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Spaid, John Wes, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Spannaus, Harry A., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Sparks, Robert H. Jr. “Butch”, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Sparling, Helena, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Spears, Nelda, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Spellings, Patrice “Pete”, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Spence, Roy M. Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Spencer, Linda, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Spilman, Wade, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - Spinelli, Joseph A., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 13)
    - Spires, A Bryan Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 14)
    - Staleski, John, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 15)
    - Stanford, Keith, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 16)
    - Stanley, Marc R., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 17)
    - Stapp, Carl, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 18)
    - Stauffer, Thomas M., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 19)
    - St. Clair, Jackie W., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 20)
    - Steen, Lias B. “Bubba”, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 21)
    - Stem, Carl H., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 22)
    - Stewart, Sam B., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 23)
    - Stiles, Mark, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 24)
    - Stokes, Aubrey D., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 25)
    - Storey, Robert, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 26)
    - Stotzer, Mary Ann, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 27)
    - Stoudt, William K. Sr., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 28)
    - Strauss, Annette, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 29)
    - Street, John, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 30)
    - Strickland, Phil D., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 31)
    - Strong, Mr. & Mrs. Jack B., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 32)
    - Strothers, John S. Sr., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 33)
    - Stuart, Frank A., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 34)
    - Sturrock, Allen, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 35)
    - Sudderth, Ben D., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 36)
    - Suits, Stacy L., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 37)
    - Sunday, Melvin, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 38)
    - Sykora, D.D., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 39)
    - Tallas, James L., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 40)
    - Taub, Henry J.N., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 41)
    - Taylor, Joe, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 42)
    - Taylor, M.A., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 43)
    - Taylor, Raymond, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 44)
    - Teague, Marvin O., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 45)
    - Team, Linda B., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 46)
    - Team, Lin B., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 47)
    - Tejeda, Frank M. Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 48)
    - Telford, Barry B., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 49)
    - Temple, Larry E., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 50)
    - Tenery, Randy, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 51)
    - Terrell, Charles T., 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 52)
    - TeVault, DeWayne, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 53)
    - Texas Delegation, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 54)
    - Texas Legislature, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 55)
    - Thaddeus, A. Peter, 1989-1990 (Box 142, Folder 56)
    - Thomas, Robert E., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Thomas, Steve, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Thomas, Zook, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Thompson, Bill M., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Thompson, Jere W., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Thrash, Joe H., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Tiede, Saralee, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Tierney, Cornelius E., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Tilley, Rice M. Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Tinsley, Eleanor, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Tolo, Kenneth W., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Toomey, Mike, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Torres, Ruben M., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - Townes, Gus Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - Townsend, Pat Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 15)
    - Townsend, Terry, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 16)
    - Townsend, Tommy, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 17)
    - Travisono, Anthony P., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 18)
    - Truan, Carlos F., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 19)
    - Truelove, Dorothy L., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 20)
    - Tucker, Deborah D., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 21)
    - Tucker, J.T., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 22)
    - Tunnell, Byron M., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 23)
    - Tunnell, Joe, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 24)
    - Turner, Carleton, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 25)
    - Turner, Marshall L. Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 26)
    - Tyndall, Marshall C., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 27)
    - Ulbricht, Walter A., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 28)
    - Ulmer, Jim, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 29)
    - Upton, Richard D., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 30)
    - Uribe, Hector, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 31)
    - Utley, Robert K. III, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 32)
    - Valigura, Keith, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 33)
    - Van Daniker, Relmond P., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 34)
    - Van Hightower, Nikki R., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 35)
    - Van Houten, George D., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 36)
    - Varner, Cal E., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 37)
    - Vautour, Roland R., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 38)
    - Vela, L. Fabian, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 39)
    - Viken, Linda Lea, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 40)
    - Von Kennel, Timothy, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 41)
    - Wade, Jack H., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 42)
    - Walker, K.P., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 43)
    - Wallace, Barbara, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 44)
    - Wallace, Jane, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 45)
    - Wallace, Ralph III, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 46)
    - Wallis, Bill W., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 47)
    - Walton, Ralph H. Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 48)
    - Ward, Joe E., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 49)
    - Ware, Browning, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 50)
    - Warner, Larry, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 51)
    - Washington, Craig A., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 52)
    - Washington, Linda, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 53)
    - Watson, Kirk P., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 54)
    - Watson, Larry, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 55)
    - Watson, Murray Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 56)
    - Waxler, Melvin E., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 57)
    - Wayne, Ralph Sr., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 58)
    - Weightman, Faith A., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 59)
    - Welch, Marcia, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 60)
    - Welch, Virgil L., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 61)
    - Weldon, William F., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 62)
    - Wells, John Calhoun, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 63)
    - Wells, William W., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 64)
    - Westbrook, Pat D., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 65)
    - Westerholm, Harvey W., 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 66)
    - Whalen, Edward L., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Whatley, Willis, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - White, Edward P., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - White, Randy, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - White, Rex H. Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Whitehead, Emmett H., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Whitehead, Joyce M., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Whitehurst, Michael, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Whitmire, Kathryn, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Whynot, Charles L., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Wied, John W., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Wieting, Leroy, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 12)
    - Wilkerson, David, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 13)
    - Wilkerson, John G. Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 14)
    - Wilkins, Clay A., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 15)
    - Williams, Eva Jean, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 16)
    - Williams, Louis B. Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 17)
    - Williams, Lyndell, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 18)
    - Williams, Meredith, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 19)
    - Williams, Monte, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 20)
    - Williams, Pat, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 21)
    - Williams, Paul J., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 22)
    - Williams, Raymond A. Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 23)
    - Williams, Robert G., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 24)
    - Williamson, L.D., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 25)
    - Williamson, Richard F., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 26)
    - Willis, Doyle, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 27)
    - Willy, John, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 28)
    - Wilson, Bobby M., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 29)
    - Wilson, Charles, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 30)
    - Wilson, Clyde A., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 31)
    - Wilson, John R., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 32)
    - Wilson, Myra, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 33)
    - Wilson, Ron, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 34)
    - Wilson, William D., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 35)
    - Winkler, Mr. & Mrs. James P., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 36)
    - Winn, Robert, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 37)
    - Wirwahn, F. Eugene, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 38)
    - Wise, Charles, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 39)
    - Wise, Charles D., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 40)
    - Wismer, Merle L., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 41)
    - Withrow, Mary Ellen, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 42)
    - Wolens, Steven D., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 43)
    - Wood, D.B., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 44)
    - Wood, Edmund R., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 45)
    - Wood, Gary E., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 46)
    - Wood, Jerry, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 47)
    - Woods, Joe M., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 48)
    - Woodson, Herbert H., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 49)
    - Woodson, J.P., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 50)
    - Wright, Charles E. Sr., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 51)
    - Wright, Peggy Wedgeworth, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 52)
    - Yarborough, Ralph W., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 53)
    - Yudof, Mark G., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 54)
    - Zaffirini, Judith, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 55)
    - Zamora, San Juanita, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 56)
    - Zepeda, Ronald L. “Ron”, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 57)
    - Zimmerman, Julian H., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 58)
    - Zimmerman, Mrs. Julian, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 59)
    - Zivley, Lane, 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 60)
    - Zottarelli, Angelo P., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 61)
    - Zuniga, Mike Jr., 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 62)
  - Media, 1975-1990; 3
    - Alpha, 1975-1986; 1
      - Aalund, Dagmar, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 1)
      - Aird, Ms. M, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 2)
      - Albright, W.L. (Bill), 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 3)
      - Alderman, Bill, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 4)
      - Aldridge, Leon, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 5)
      - Allen, Ted, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 6)
      - Allred, Keith, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 7)
      - Amarillo Daily News — Editorial, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 8)
      - Amberg, Thomas L., 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 9)
      - Ambrose, Jay, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 10)
      - Ammons, Josh, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 11)
      - Anderson, John, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 12)
      - Arambula, Odie, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 13)
      - Aramendia, Felicia, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 14)
      - Armstead, Bob, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 15)
      - Arnold, Ann, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 16)
      - Arnold, Jerry, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 17)
      - Ashby, Lynn, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 18)
      - Ashley, Olin, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 19)
      - Austin, Brux, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 20)
      - Austin, Linda, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 21)
      - Autry, Milton, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 22)
      - Axelson, Bob, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 23)
      - Bagatelles, Don, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 24)
      - Baggarly, H.M., 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 25)
      - Baggett, Donnis, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 26)
      - Baker, Frank, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 27)
      - Baldwin, Charles E., 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 28)
      - Barbee, Christopher (Chris), 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 29)
      - Barbee, Fred V., Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 30)
      - Barker, M. Dale, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 31)
      - Barlow, Jim, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 32)
      - Barnstone, Gertrude, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 33)
      - Barta, Carolyn, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 34)
      - Barton, Bob Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 35)
      - Barton, Jeff, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 36)
      - Bass, Sam, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 37)
      - Baxter, Gordon, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 38)
      - Bayoud, George S., 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 39)
      - Behringer, Daniel, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 40)
      - Belcher, James J., 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 41)
      - Bennett, Scott, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 42)
      - Bentley, Robert, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 43)
      - Berkebile, Phillip, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 44)
      - Besaw, Larry, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 45)
      - Bifano, Michelle, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 46)
      - Blase, Les, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 47)
      - Bode, William, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 48)
      - Bonavita, Fred W., 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 49)
      - Booker, Don, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 50)
      - Bordelon, Ann, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 51)
      - Bowman, Harry, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 52)
      - Bradley, Ann, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 53)
      - Branch, John, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 54)
      - Brann, June K., 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 55)
      - Brewer, Orlin, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 56)
      - Bridges, Deborah T., 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 57)
      - Broiles, Barnes H. Sr., 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 58)
      - Brown, Leon, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 59)
      - Brown, William A., 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 60)
      - Broyles, William D., 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 61)
      - Bruce, Jeff, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 62)
      - Bruce, Robert, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 63)
      - Brunner, Dean, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 64)
      - Bryant, Henry, 1975-1986 (Box 145, Folder 65)
      - Buckel, Walter, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 1)
      - Bureau Chiefs — Capitol Press Corp, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 2)
      - Burka, Paul, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 3)
      - Burnett, Mr. & Mrs. Wesley, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 4)
      - Butcher, Lee, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 5)
      - Butler, Jack, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 6)
      - Byers, Bo, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 7)
      - Byrd, Ken, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 8)
      - Calhoun, Ronald O, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 9)
      - Callaway, Wilbur, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 10)
      - Calmes, Jackie, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 11)
      - Calvit, Joe, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 12)
      - Camper, Buddy, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 13)
      - Cannon, Sandy, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 14)
      - Cardwell, Cary, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 15)
      - Carracino, Theo, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 16)
      - Carter, O.K., 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 17)
      - Casebolt, Floyd, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 18)
      - Caudell, Susan, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 19)
      - Charles, Dennis, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 20)
      - Chatmas, J. C. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 21)
      - Chessher, Earl, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 22)
      - Chick, Fern, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 23)
      - Childs, Hyman, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 24)
      - Clapp, Kenyon F., 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 25)
      - Clark, Herman, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 26)
      - Clark, Lee, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 27)
      - Clyde, Calvin Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 28)
      - Clyde, Nelson, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 29)
      - Collier, Everett D., 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 30)
      - Collins, Albert T., 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 31)
      - Collins, John E., 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 32)
      - Collins, Robert, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 33)
      - Collyns, W. H., 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 34)
      - Combs, Bill, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 35)
      - Comedy, Bill, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 36)
      - Conklin, Matt, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 37)
      - Conway, Pat, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 38)
      - Cooke, W. H. (Bill), 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 39)
      - Copelin, Laylan, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 40)
      - Craig, Bob, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 41)
      - Cramer, Rodger, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 42)
      - Crawford, John, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 43)
      - Crogan, Larry, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 44)
      - Cross, Riley, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 45)
      - Cullum, Lee, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 46)
      - Culp, Clint, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 47)
      - Cunningham, T. H., 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 48)
      - Curtis, Edwin S., 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 49)
      - Curtis, Gregory, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 50)
      - Dale, Allan, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 51)
      - Dallas Morning News, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 52)
      - Danner, Dan, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 53)
      - Davis, Jim, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 54)
      - Davis, Stewart, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 55)
      - DeBolt, V. Lyle, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 56)
      - Dees, Margie, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 57)
      - Devall, Charles K., 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 58)
      - Dickson, Bob, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 59)
      - Diehl, Kemper, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 60)
      - Dietel, Norman J., 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 61)
      - Dolcefino, Wayne, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 62)
      - Donovan, J. C., 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 63)
      - Dorsey, Russell F., 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 64)
      - Dotson, Tom, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 65)
      - Douthit, Jack S., 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 66)
      - Dozier, William E. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 67)
      - Duffy, Gavan, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 68)
      - Dufner, Ed, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 69)
      - Dugger, Ronnie, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 70)
      - Duke, Vicki S., 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 71)
      - Dungan, Troy, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 72)
      - Dunham, Rick, 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 73)
      - Durham, Paul M., 1975-1986 (Box 146, Folder 74)
      - Edgar, Aaron, 1975-1986 (Box 147, Folder 1)
      - Editorial Page Editor, 1975-1986 (Box 147, Folder 2)
      - Edmondson, Gary, 1975-1986 (Box 147, Folder 3)
      - Elder, Bob Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 147, Folder 4)
      - Ellis, Virginia, 1975-1986 (Box 147, Folder 5)
      - Ellzey, Sharon, 1975-1986 (Box 147, Folder 6)
      - Epperson, Wayne, 1975-1986 (Box 147, Folder 7)
      - Eskew, Pat, 1975-1986 (Box 147, Folder 8)